Konvitz, Milton R., Liberian Codification Project /4039 L
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Milton R. Konvitz Liberian Codification Project
1962-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Konvitz, Milton R.
/4039 L
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Records (documents), correspondence.
Boxes 1-3, 8-12, and 15-31 of this collection were transferred to the Cornell Law Library in 2005. Please consult with the Law Library Reference Librarian for these additional materials.
7952328
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Biographical / Historical
March 12, 1908-September 5, 2003 Milton Konvitz, a Cornell University faculty member and authority on constitutional and labor law, and civil and human rights, died Sept. 5 at the age of 95. Konvitz was a founding faculty member in the School of Industrial and Labor Relations from 1946 until his retirement in 1973. He was also a professor in Cornell's Law School. Konvitz is perhaps best known for his American Ideals course, which he taught to more than 8,000 students over the course of his career, never giving the same lecture twice. "I saw the U.S. Constitution as it has been interpreted as a magnificent depository of our ideals, both individual and social," he said. His course exposed students to the great intellectual thinkers and philosophers throughout history whose writings had shaped those ideals. They included Sophocles, whose play Antigone is Cornell's New Student Reading Project this year. One student he influenced was U.S. Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg, Cornell Class of 1954, who considers him a mentor. At Cornell Konvitz also was a founder of the university's Department of Near Eastern Studies and Program of Jewish Studies. "I felt it was essential for a college interested in the humanities not to leave out Hebrew language and literature," he said. "And the knowledge of Jewish history, which began 4,000 years ago and has contributed to civilization no less than Greek, Roman or English history, is important to today's students-Jewish and non-Jewish." He often hosted students at his Ithaca home and helped start the first Kosher dining option at Cornell, Young Israel House. In addition, for nearly 30 years he directed the Liberian Codification Project, which drew up the official body of statutory laws that is still in force in the Republic of Liberia today, despite the current political upheaval there. Konvitz also edited the opinions of Liberia's Supreme Court and received the Grand Band of the Order of the Star of Africa, the highest award given to foreigners, as well as an honorary degree from the University of Liberia, one of seven honorary degrees he received in his lifetime. Active as a scholar and writer until his death, he wrote books and articles on American constitutional law that won him wide recognition and were cited in U.S. Supreme Court opinions. Among his nine books is Fundamental Liberties of a Free People: Religion, Speech, Press, Assembly, which was republished earlier this year with an expanded introduction by him that is strongly critical of the Rehnquist Supreme Court. Other books include A Century of Civil Rights (1983) and Judaism and Human Rights (2nd ed. 2001). He also edited a dozen volumes, including two on American philosopher Ralph Waldo Emerson, whose thinking shaped his views. One Emersonian idea he absorbed was that readers give life to books, which Konvitz recast as follows: "It is in their hearing that students bring life to the words, the thoughts, the teacher." Konvitz was born in Safed, Palestine (now Israel ), in 1908, the son of a rabbi. He immigrated to the United States in 1915 and became a naturalized citizen in 1926. He received a bachelor's degree in 1929 and a law degree in 1930, both from New York University, and a Ph.D. in philosophy from Cornell in 1933. Before joining Cornell's faculty, he was one of three assistant general counsels to Thurgood Marshall at the NAACP Legal Defense Fund for three years. He is survived by his wife, Mary, of Oakhurst, N.J.; a brother, Phillip, of Elberon, N.J.; a son and daughter-in-law, Josef and Isa, of Paris, France; and two grandsons, Eli and Ezra. Josef Konvitz, who grew up in Ithaca, is now an official at the Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development.
Scope and Contents
Boxes 1-3, 8-12, and 15-31 of this collection were transferred to the Cornell Law Library in 2005. Please consult with the Law Library Reference Librarian for these additional materials.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3033: Milton R. Konvitz Liberian Project Files /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers /4039 AV: Milton R. Konvitz American Ideals Lectures Audio-Visual Materials /4039 B: Milton R. Konvitz Additional Papers /4039m: Milton R. Konvitz Tribute to Irving M. Ives and Edmund Ezra Day /4085: Milton R. Konvitz Additional Papers /4220m: Milton Konvitz Additional Papers /4289 AV: ILR School Alumni Affairs and Development Audio-Visual Materials /4297: ILR School Biography Files /4341: Milton R. Konvitz Collections 6047: Archives Information File
Konvitz, Milton R.(Milton Ridvas), 1908-2003; Liberian Codification Project
7952328
- Old Correspondence - Miscellaneous; Court Apprenticeship - State Dept. Washington (Box 4)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Court Administrator Apprenticeship. Spring 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    May and June 1959
  - Liberian Codification Project. Courts Commission. June 1957 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    May and June 1957
  - Liberian Codification Project. Commission, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Ithaca. August 20 1955 - 1957. Contains one photograph
  - "Regulation of Insurance in the Republic of Liberia: A Study and Proposed Insurance Law for the Republic of Liberia", 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Checci and Company, Washington, DC. May 1967
  - "Bibliographical Introduction to Legal History and Ethnology of Liberia" Drafts and Papers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Edited by John Gilissen. French and English
  - Liberian Codification Project. Legislative Drafting Apprenticeship., 1960-1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Liberian Codification Project. International Labor Organization Fellowships, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    August 26 1960 - September 18 1963
  - Liberian Codification Project. International Labor Organization. Portuguese Situation, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - AID Program. Washington, DC, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    December 6 1962 - March 15 1963
  - Cornell Scholarship. Rocheforte L. Weeks Centennial Scholarship, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Newspaper Clipping. November 27 1962
  - Liberian Codification Project. Liberian Tax Law. "Taxes Around the World". Foosaner, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    December 8 1961 - June 1 1964
  - American Foundation for Tropical Medicine, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Correspondence with Liberia. Liberian Law Reports, 1933-1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    1933 - April 1 1966
  - Liberian Codification Project. Correspondence with Liberia. Cumulative Supplement, 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    July 18 1957 - May 10 1960
  - Liberian Codification Project. Washington Foreign Operations Administration and the International Cooperation Administration. WE Morgan, Jr. Julius Kessler. Harry F Hemmerich, 1953-1956 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    April 3 1953 - April 23 1956
  - Liberian Codification Project. James L Gibbs, Jr., 1954-1965 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    October 5 1954 - July 12 1965
  - Liberian Codification Project. State Department. Washington DC, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    January 14 1952 - November 13 1953
- Old Correspondence - Liberian and Liberian Organizations; Liberian Embassy - Rockefort Weeks (Box 5)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Liberian Embassy. Washington, DC, 1954-1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    October 15 1954 - December 23 1963
  - Liberian Codification Project. US Ambassador to Liberia. Edward R Dudley. Richard L Jones, 1951-1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    November 19 1951 - January 14 1966
  - Liberian Codification Project. Liberian Consulate General. United Nations (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Liberian Services, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Legal Education in Africa. Dean John S Bainbridge, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    October 1962 - November 24 1964
  - Liberian Codification Project. International Labor Office. Washington DC, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    February 2 1962 - April 17 1964
  - Liberian Codification Project. Government Library, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    March 5 1962 - July 16 1962
  - Liberian Codification Project. Africa Student Study and Work Camp Project NYC, 1958-1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    May 6 1958 - May 1 1968
  - Liberian Codification Project. Joseph J F Chesson, Attorney general. J Dossen Richards, Acting Attorney General, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    July 14 1961 - August 10 1967
  - Liberian Codification Project. Edward R. Moore, 1958-1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    November 11 1958 - March 21 1966
  - Liberian Codification Project. William V.S. Tubman, President, 1954-1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    July 1 1954 - November 27 1967
  - Liberian Codification Project. C Abayomi Cassell, Attorney General, 1952-1959 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    June 9 1952 - May 1 1959
  - Liberian Codification Project. Joseph W Garber, Attorney General, 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    April 8 1958 - September 4 1961
  - Dean Joseph Garber. Law School, University of Liberia, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    July 11 1960 - October 25 1968
  - Liberian Codification Project. Weeks, Rocheforte L, 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    November 9 1955 - February 17 1958
  - Weeks, Rocheforte L. President, University of Liberia, 1959-1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Liberian Students. Baker, J Nyema. Special Student, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    October 19 1961 - February 20 1965
  - Liberian Students. Beyan, Timothy Zeze (ILO), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Liberian Students. Rogers, Edwin Lahai (ILO), 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    May 24 1962 - October 2 1963
  - Liberian Students. Birch, Caesar W, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Liberian Students. Smallwood, Benjamin, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    February 14 1962
  - Liberian Students. Cornell Law School. Tubman, Winston (September 1963 admission), 1962-1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    December 2 1962 - April 24 1968
  - Liberian Students. Wisseh, Francis F (prospective), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    February 1964
  - Liberian Students. Wordsworth, A Benjamin (to enter Law School Fall 1961), 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    July 13 1960 - June 11 1964
  - Liberian Project. Agreement regarding students. Cornell University, United States, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Liberian Students. Cornell. Cooper, Julius, 1958-1965 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Liberian Students. Cornell. Henries, George, 1958-1963 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    March 19 1958 - November 7 1963
  - Liberian Students. Cornell. Weeks, Rocheforte L. Student, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    November 14 1952 - June 2 1954
- Old Correspondence - Project Staff and Cornell University Officials and Depts.; Cornell Univ. Press - Margaret Rosenzweig (Box 6)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Cornell University Press: Liberian Code of Laws Cumulative Supplement, 1954-1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Koss, Milton, 1962-1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    April 6 1962 - December 29 1966
  - Liberian Codification Project. Staff. Steven Werner, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    September 10 1964 - December 19 1967
  - Liberian Codification Project. Rosenzweig, Simon, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    October 16 1961 - May 27 1969
  - Liberian Codification Project. Cornell University Press: Royalty Reports, 1956-1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    June 30 1956 - August 15 1961
  - Liberian Codification Project. University President and other Administrative Personnel, 1958-1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    January 11 1958 - February 16 1965
  - Milton R Konvitz Trip to Liberia., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    June 26 - August 1 1966
  - Liberian Codification Project. Annual Reports of the Director, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Milton R Konvitz Trip to Liberia, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    September to October 1959, 1962
  - Inquiries re Liberian Law Reports, 1962-1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    May 4 1962 - February 3 1966
  - Liberian Codification Project. University of Liberia. Law Library. Cornell Affiliation, 1955-1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - University of Liberia. Contract: USA, Government of Liberia and Cornell University, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - University of Liberia. Cornell Affiliation, 1959-1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Decoration by Liberian Government. Washington, DC, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    July 17 1957 - July 1 1958
  - Liberian Codification Project. Quarterly Progress Reports (extra copies), 1952-1956 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    September 2 1952 - February 7 1956
  - Liberian Codification Project. Contract Forms, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    August to October 1955
  - Liberian Law Project. Library Agreement, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Agreement re Project. United States and Cornell University, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    June 2 1952
  - Liberian Project. Miscellaneous Laws, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    May 29 1953
  - "A Law Library for the Republic of Liberia" Draft, 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Transportation for the 1952 Trip to Liberia (Box 6, Folder 21)
    March, April and May 1952
  - Liberian Project. George M. Johnson. Thurgood Marshall, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    May 6 and July 1 1952
  - Liberian Project. Agreement re School of Law. United States and Cornell University, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Liberian Codification Project. ILR School: Administrative Assistant 1st Agreement, 1952-1957 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    July 8 1952 - January 12 1957
  - Liberian Codification Project. University President, Vice President For Research and other Administrative Personnel, 1952-1956 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    June 5 1952 - May 14 1956
  - Konvitz Letter, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    May 14 1952
  - Konvitz Letter, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    June 10 1952
  - Konvitz Letter. Monrovia, Liberia, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    July 30 1952
  - Liberian Codification Project. Staff Trip to Liberia. Fall 1960 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    July 25 1960 - October 18 1960
  - Liberian Codification Project. Knickerbocker, Helaine, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    March 2 1959 - July 19 1962
  - Liberian Codification Project. Staff. Landis, Betsy, 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    January 7 1959 - February 11 1963
  - Liberian Codification Project. Landis, Betsy, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    January 23 1957 - December 17 1958
  - Liberian Codification Project. Staff. Landis, Betsy., 1948-1956 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    August 11 1948 - December 19 1956
  - Plant, Nancy Helm., 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    October 7 1959 - June 25 1965
  - Liberian Codification Project. Staff. Rosenzweig, Margaret L, 1958-1963 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    December 31 1958 - December 24 1963
- Old Correspondence - Staff - Current Liberian Correspondence; Margaret Rosenzweig - Murray Ross; E. Barnard - Miscellaneous Organizations (Liberian) (Box 7)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Staff. Rosenzweig, Margaret L, 1952-1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    May 28 1952 - December 9 1958
  - Liberian Codification Project. Staff. Rosenzweig, Margaret L, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    January to December 1967
  - Liberian Codification Project. Assistants. Beck, Mary, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    March 10 1953 - December 2 1964
  - Liberian Codification Project. Assistants. Greenbaum, Edward S, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    February 25 - March 11 1954
  - Greenberg, Jack, 1952-1958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    November 10 1952 - October 16 1958
  - Murray, Pauli, 1952-1959 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    April 16 1952 - July 28 1959
  - Barnard, E. Acting Minister of Justice, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    September 26 1974 - July 2 1976
  - Barnes, Roland. Assistant Attorney General, 1966-1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    July 27 1966 - January 14 1980
  - Oliver Bright. Minister of Justice, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    July 2 1976 - November 29 1978
  - Chess on, Joseph JF. Minister of Justice, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    June 13 1979 - March 12 1980
  - Dormu, Alfonso. Minister of Justice for Codification, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Flemister, E Cassell. Minister of Justice for Codification, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    July 13 1977 - January 8 1980
  - Grimes, Rudolph. State Department, 1952-1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    June 27 1952 - January 4 1972
  - Henries, George. Attorney General, 1971-1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    May 7 1971 - April 1 1980
  - Morgan, Lawrence A. Minister of Justice, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    December 20 1974 - January 3 1977
  - Pierre, James A. Chief Justice, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    January 6 1975 - March 12 1980
  - Tolbert, William R, Jr. President, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Weeks, Rocheforte L. President, University of Liberia, 1966-1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    January 5 1966 - October 26 1972
  - Law School, University of Liberia, 1967-1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    August 1967 - July 30 1973
  - Liberian Personnel, Miscellaneous, 1973-1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    September 10 1973 - March 28 1980
  - Students, Miscellaneous, 1968-1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    January 16 1968 - March 3 1980
  - Barnes, Roland Jr, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    November 10 1971 - June 30 1972
  - Boldoe, Frank T, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    October 17 1966 - August 29 1967
  - Garber, Joseph W, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    January 6 1968 - September 30 1969
  - Jomah, Joseph, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    May 28 1966 - September 28 1967
  - Morris, John, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    June 25 1973 - January 2 1975
  - Liberian Students. Pierre, James A. A. Jr., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Codification Trainees, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Liberian Codification. School of Oriental and African Studies, London, 1958-1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    February 27 1958 - September 20 1977
  - African Law Association, 1971-1979 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    September 1971 - December 6 1979
  - Liberian Codification. African Studies Association, 1971-1980 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    February 25 1971 - April 30 1980
  - Liberian Codification. ILO Geneva, 1966-1974 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    February 16 1966 - April 10 1974
  - African Law Association, 1971-1979 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Liberian Codification. ILO Washington, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    November 9 1965 - June 2-3 1967
  - Liberian Codification. Liberian Embassy, 1964-1974 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    January 24 1964 - May 2 1974
  - Liberian Codification. Liberian Consulate General. UN, 1952-1980 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    May 7 1952 - February 15 1980
  - Liberian Codification. Liberian Services, Inc., 1956-1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    September 19 1956 - September 19 1979
  - Liberian Codification. Miscellaneous, 1962-1977 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    October 25 1962 - January 3 1977
  - Liberian Codification. Miscellaneous Organizations, 1966-1974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    1966 - June 5 1974
- Newspaper Clippings re Liberia, 1952-1980; Correspondence - Cornell Univ. Press re production of volumes; Correspondence - School and Faculty (Box 13)
  - Liberian Codification. Labor. Newspaper Clippings, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Liberia Newspaper Stories, 1952-1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    1952 - April 14 1980
  - Cornell University press. Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    October 2 1973 - February 7 1978
  - Liberian Codification. Cornell University Press Royalty Reports, 1965-1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    1965 - January 30 1973
  - Liberian Codification. Cornell University Press Agreements, 1967-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    August 7 1967 - November 9 1979
  - Liberian Codification. Liberian Law Reports. People to Recognize, 1957-1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    October 18 1957 - November 1977
  - Liberian Project. Inquires and Requests Code and Liberian Law Report, 1957-1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    November 26 1957 - January 4 1980
  - Liberian Codification. Miscellaneous Printing Matters, 1955-1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    January 20 1955 - March 22 1973
  - Liberian Project. Shipment of Materials, Dean of Ithaca, 1963-1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    June 26 1963 - March 16 1976
  - Liberian Project. ILR School Memos, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    January 11 1977 - April 24 1979
  - Liberian Project. General Staff, 1965-1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    May 10 1965 - June 2 1980
  - Liberian Project. Staff Travel and Miscellaneous Expenses, 1967-1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    May 8 1967 - June 2 1980
  - Liberian Codification Project. 'Citation for Dr. Milton R. Konvitz", 1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    September 26 1959
  - Liberia. Articles Regarding Project Staff (Box 13, Folder 14)
    9 white pamphlets and 23 green
  - Rosenzweig, Margaret, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Rosenzweig, Margaret, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Staff Vacations, 1964-1977 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Liberian Project. Staff, Milton Koss, 1973-1980 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Liberian Project. Staff, S Rosenzweig, 1965-1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Chasen, Robert, 1971-1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Financial Reports of Project - Correspondence/Liberians (Box 14)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Quarterly Reports, 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Monthly Financial Statements, 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Liberian Codification Project. Agreements, 1968-1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Tubman, William V.S., President of Liberia, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Cassell Case, 1962-1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Pierre, James A.A. Attorney General, 1968-1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Pierre, James A.A. Attorney General, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Liberian Project. Honorable James A. A. Pierre, Attorney General, 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Liberian Project. Staff, Margaret Rosenzweig, 1969-1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Rosenzweig, Margaret, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Liberian Project. Staff, S. Werner, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 12)